Author: Yiwen Li

Readme:

This is a sample of my code.
Here is a brief explanation for the files included:

1.AI.zip: code from projects I did in “Advanced AI” class at the University of Michigan.
2.Android.zip: code from a project about “Android permission-based security model”. 
3.Compiler.zip: code from a project implementing a MiniJava Compiler. 
4.Crypto.zip: code about Cryptosystem implementation and Attack Schemes.
5.Phishing.zip: code from Phishing project, which focused on collecting and analyzing data from malicious and benign websites to build classifiers for users to identify potential malicious websites with relatively high accuracy. It also includes a paper I wrote as a summary for this project.


Thank you~

